#### Contato

964 972 863 (Mobile) henrique.manuel.marques.rit a@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/henriquerita-90224a29 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/henriquerita8 (Portfolio)

### Principais competências

Flash

Illustrator

Dreamweaver

### Languages

Portuguese (Professional Working) English (Professional Working)

# henrique rita

Web designer, Ecommerce, graphic, ui / ux Lisbon Area, Portugal

### Resumo

Experienced Web Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in E-commerce Optimization, Graphics, User Experience (UX), Logo Design, and E-commerce. Strong arts and design professional with a lincenciatura focused in Design de Produção Visual from IADE.

### Experiência

Hexangulo Advertising

4 anos

Web Designer agosto de 2016 - Present

Graphic Designer 2016 - 2016 (menos de um ano)

Lógikarmonia consultores, Lda. Graphic Web Designer 2012 - 2013 (1 ano) Alcochete

Alba-Associação Ayurvédcia Luso-Brasileira Graphic Web Designer 2010 - 2012 (2 anos)

GRANDE MERCADO

Web Designer 2009 - 2010 (1 ano)

Alcochete

ARTAVER - Eventos e publicidade Graphic Designer 2008 - 2008 (menos de um ano) AQUATRO - Centro de Imagem Graphic Designer 2008 - 2008 (menos de um ano)

IADE Designer

2003 - 2007 (4 anos)

## Formação acadêmica

**IADE** 

lincenciatura, Design de Produção Visual · (2003 - 2007)

the.edge

Flag